Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-18, Box 22-45)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-18)
    - Babes in Arms (1937) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - [Sketches for Babes In Arms], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Verse [I wish I were in] love again," "[Unidentified]," "[All at once]: Never love," "Rhythm" (from André Charlot revue Please!, 1933) p. [2]: "[Where or when]," "[Johnny one note]," "[Unidentified]," "[Unidentified]," "[All dark people]" p. [3]: "[Unidentified]," "[Unidentified]," "Imagine" p. [4]: "[Imagine]: verse," "Babes in arms," "[Unidentified]," "[Unidentified]," "[Unidentified]," "[I wish I were] in love again" (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Bad Habits of 1925, musical revue, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - College baby!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil & ink, no lyric; [4] p.; Lyric by Robert Simon (Box-folder 2/11)
      - I'd like to take you home, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Note: later used in The Girl Friend (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Mah jong maid, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p.; Lyric by Herbert Fields (Box-folder 2/13)
      - The merry merry, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil & ink, no lyric; [2] p.; On t.p.: "Opening" and "1"; Uniform title: The merrie merrie (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Silver threads, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 5 p. (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Betsy (1926) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Birds on high see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Bugle blow see: [Sketches for Betsy]
      - If I were you see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Is my girl refined?, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p.; Note: dropped before New York opening (Box-folder 2/16)
      - The Kitzel engagement see: Opening ensemble see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Nations patters, Holograph condensed score in pencil; 8 p.; Includes: "Irish" "Italian" "Russian" "Chinese" (Box-folder 2/17)
      - One of us should be two see: [Sketches for Betsy]
      - Opening ensemble, or, [The Kitzel engagement], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 8 p. (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Shuffle!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p.; On t.p.: "Intro I-II" (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Sing! See also: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 2/20)
      - This funny world see: [Sketches for Betsy]
      - [Sketches for Betsy], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Note: melody for "Mosk[owitz] open[ing] patter" appears to fit the lyric for "At the Saskatchewan," which was cut before the opening; Includes: p. [1]: "[Bugle blow]: Verse of 'American,'" "[One of us should be two]," "[Unidentified]" p. [2]: "[This funny world]," "[Unidentified]," [Bugle blow: refrain]" p. [3]: "Burn up!," "[Unidentified]," "Dummy march" (from Betsy or Peggy-Ann) p. [4]: "Irish," "Russian," "[Tramping along]" (cut from Peggy-Ann), "Mosk[owitz] open[ing] patter" (Box-folder 2/21)
    - The Boys from Syracuse (1938; film 1940) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - [Ballet], Holograph sketches in pencil; [1] p.; On back: unidentified holograph sketch in pencil (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Big brother, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; On back: notes on the instrumentation in blue and red pencil (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Come with me, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Dear old Syracuse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Falling in love with love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Finale act one, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 11 p. (Box-folder 2/27)
      - The Greeks have no word for it See also: [Sketches for Higher and Higher], Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: from the 1940 film version of The Boys from Syracuse (Box-folder 2/28)
      - He and she, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/29)
      - He had twins!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [14] p.; On cover: "Opening" (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Ladies of the evening, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Oh, Diogenes, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/32)
      - The shortest day of the year, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/33)
      - Sing for your supper, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Note: melody sketch in light pencil at bottom of p. 4 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - What can you do with a man?, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/35)
      - Who are you?, Holograph piano-vocal score (verse only) in pencil; [1] p.; Laid in: carbon copy of typed lyric sheet; [1] p.; Note: from the 1940 film version of The Boys from Syracuse (Box-folder 2/36)
      - Who are you? See also: [M.S. 11] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Note: verse different than above, but the same as verse of "From another world," from Higher and Higher; Note: from the 1940 film version of The Boys from Syracuse (Box-folder 2/36)
      - [You have cast your] shadow on the sea, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/37)
      - [Sketches for The Boys from Syracuse], Holograph sketches in pencil; [10] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Come with me," "Patter" p. [2]: "Verse [Oh,] Diogenes," "[Falling in love with love]: Serving" p. [3]: "He and she verse" p. [5]: "Trio" p. [6]: "[You have cast your shadow on the sea]," "[This can't be love]" p. [7]: "What can you do with a man" p. [8]: "Opening act I," "Verse [You have cast your] shadow on the sea," "[Dear old] Syracuse" p. [9]: "The shortest day [of the year]," "[Oh, Diogenes]" p. [10]: "Big brother," "Trio Sing for your supper" (Box-folder 2/38)
    - By Jupiter (1942) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - The boy I left behind me, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet entitled "Opening act one"; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Careless rhapsody, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Everything I've got, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Finaletto (Act II), Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheets (2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Fool meets fool, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with annotation in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/6)
      - The gateway of the Temple of Minerva see: Temple of Minerva
      - Here's a hand, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Jupiter forbid, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [5] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Life was monotonous, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Life with Father, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Nobody's heart, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil & type; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Nothing to do but relax, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Temple dance, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 3/13)
      - The Temple of Minerva, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet entitled "In the gateway of the temple of Minerva"; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Wait till you see her See also: [Sketches for Oklahoma!], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Carousel (1945; film 1956) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Blow high, blow low, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Carrousel, Holograph sketch in pencil; 5 p.; On t.p.: "Intro 'Liliom'"; Uniform title: Carousel waltz (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Carrousel, Holograph piano score in pencil; 13 p.; Uniform title: Carousel waltz (Box-folder 3/17)
      - The carousel waltz See also: [Sketches for Hallelujah, I'm a Bum], Ozalid of copyist's ms. piano score; 18 p.; Uniform title: Carousel waltz (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Geraniums; Stonecutters; What's the use of wond'rin', Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 9 p.; Note: actual title for "Stonecutters" is "There's nothin' so bad for a woman"; Uniform title: Geraniums in the winder (Box-folder 3/18)
      - The highest judge of all, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Scene Billy and Julie; If I loved you, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 14 p.; Uniform title: If I loved you (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Act one, scene three opening; June is bustin' out all over, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 10 p.; Uniform title: June is bustin' out all over (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Julie and Carrie sequence; Mister Snow, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, incomplete lyric; 11 p.; Uniform title: Mister Snow (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Reprise Mr. Snow, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 5 p.; Uniform title: Mister Snow (Box-folder 3/22)
      - A real nice clambake, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Soliloquy, Holograph sketch in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Soliloquy, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 14 p. + [1] p. insert; Note: includes a [1] p. typed lyric sheet to accompany the insert (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Stonecutters cut it on stone see: Geraniums in the winder
      - There's nothin' so bad for a woman see: Geraniums in the winder
      - 2 little people, Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [1] p.; Note: lyric suggests a relation to "If I loved you"; Uniform title: Two little people (Box-folder 3/25)
      - What's the use of wond'rin' see: Geraniums in the winder
      - Carrie and Mister Snow; When the children are asleep, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 8 p.; Uniform title: When the children are asleep (Box-folder 3/26)
      - You'll never walk alone, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Chee-Chee (1928) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - I must love you see: Send for me in Simple Simon
      - [Various titles] see: [M.S. 2] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
    - The Chinese Lantern (1922) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Chinese march, Holograph piano score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 3/28)
      - I want to be a grocer, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Wee little china rose, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [5] p.; Lyrics by Laurence Housman (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Cinderella (1957) television musical, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Do I love you (because you're beautiful), Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Do I love you, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: also includes sketch fragment for "Impossible" (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Fol-de-rol, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Fol-de-rol, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Gavotte!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 4/3)
      - If I weren't king see: [Sketches for Cinderella]
      - Impossible, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Impossible, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/4)
      - In my own little corner, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Corner, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/5)
      - A lovely night, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/6)
      - [A lovely night], Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Mother and daughters' march, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Prince is giving a ball, Holograph sketch (with lyric) in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Scene before In my own little corner, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil (including rhythmic notations); p. 64-66 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Ten minutes ago, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Waltz for a ball, Holograph piano score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Waltz!, Holograph sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 4/11)
      - [Sketches for Cinderella], Holograph sketches in pencil; [3] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Cinderella," "12 bells or chimes on [half note] A" p. [2]: "Mother and daughters' march" p. [3]: "Ten minutes ago" (Box-folder 4/12)
      - [Sketches for Cinderella], Holograph sketches in pencil, some lyric; [4] p.; Includes: Ex[i]t march If I weren't king: dummy Intro to Lovely night (Box-folder 4/12)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets, one with sketch material in pencil, most with 2 copies; [7] p.; Includes: [Do I love you (because you're beautiful)]: Are you beautiful because I love you? Impossible In my own little corner Ten minutes ago (Box-folder 4/13)
    - A Connecticut Yankee (1927 & 1943 revival) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Can't you do a friend a favor, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Let's both go home and kiss our mothers see: [Sketches for A Connecticut Yankee]
      - My heart stood still see: [M.S. 3] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Nothing's wrong, Holograph piano-vocal score and sketch in pencil, no lyric; [3] p.; Note: 4 measure unidentified piano sketch on back (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Someone should tell them see: [Sketches for One Dam Thing After Another]
      - This is my night to howl, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Thou swell see: [Sketches for A Connecticut Yankee]
      - To keep my love alive, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 4/17)
      - You always love the same girl, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p. (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Love the same girl, Holograph sketch in pencil, partial lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 4/18)
      - You are what I need see: [Sketches for A Connecticut Yankee]
      - [Sketches for A Connecticut Yankee], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: [Can't you do a friend a] favor [This is my night to] howl [Unidentified] (Box-folder 4/19)
      - [Sketches for A Connecticut Yankee], Holograph sketches in pencil; [2] p.; Includes: Let's both go home and kiss our mothers [Thou swell]: Thou sweet [Thou swell]: Sweet [You are] what I need (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Dancing Lady (1933) film, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Dancing lady see: [M.S. 7] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES see: [Sketches for Hollywood Party]
      - That's the rhythm of the day see: [M.S. 7] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
    - Dancing Pirate (1936) film, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Are you my love? see: [M.S. 10] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
    - Dearest Enemy (1925) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Bye and bye, Photocopy of holograph piano-vocal score, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Old enough to love, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Old enough to love, Holograph piano score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/21)
      - Opening act one, or, [Heigh-ho, lackaday], Holograph piano score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Do I Hear a Waltz? (1965) lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
      - Interlude -- Perhaps, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Uniform title: Bargaining (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Do I hear a waltz?, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, partial lyric; [3] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Do I hear a waltz, Holograph sketch in pencil, some lyric; [2] p.; Note: 2 sketches, "Lover to lover" and "American Adventure," crossed out at top of page (Box-folder 4/24)
      - [Do I hear a waltz?], Holograph sketch in pencil, with lyric; [1] p.; At top: "Unused notes"; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p.; Note: this lyric was originally written by Sondheim for consideration in what became Anyone Can Whistle; when it was not used there, Sondheim later presented it to Rodgers for consideration in their show. (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Everybody loves Leona, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Leona, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; At top: "Used notes"; Note: includes a crossed out sketch for "Planes," i.e., "What do we do? We fly!" (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Here we are again, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Last week the English (This week Americans), Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil, including 3 measures of sketch material on back; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Last week the English, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/27)
      - American tag, Holograph piano-vocal sketch in pencil; 2 p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Moon in my window, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/28)
      - No understand, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Photocopy of ozalid of copyist's ms. piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil; 2 p.; Note: dated 12/14/64; Typed script portion including lyric, annotations in pencil; [7] p. (Box-folder 4/29)
      - [No understand], Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Perfectly lovely couple, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, partial lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Perhaps, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Philadelphia, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Philadelphia, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/32)
      - San Marco, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p.; At top: "Unused notes"; Note: holograph sketch in pencil for "Alt. some people" on p. [2] (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Someone like you, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed production notes with annotations in ink and holograph sketch in ink for "Someone like you"; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Someone like you: act I, scene 3, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Someone woke up, Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score in ink with holograph coda and insert material in pencil, lyrics in pencil; [4] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Someone woke up, Holograph piano sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Stay, Holograph piano-vocal sketch in pencil, partial lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Stay: coda, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/36)
      - [Stay], Holograph lyric sketch (4 lines) in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Stay -- Interlude, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; At top: "Unused ms."; On back: holograph sketch material (crossed out) (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Take the moment, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with annotations in pencil, including a 4 measure melody sketch; [1] p.; Laid in: holograph lyric sketch in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Thank you so much, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheets (2), one with annotations in pencil, the other of 1st refrain only; [1] p. each (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Thank you so much: verse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, last 4 measures crossed out; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/38)
      - I was thinking, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; 2 p.; Uniform title: Thinking (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Two by two: verse, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil include rhythmic notations on the back; [1] p. (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Two by two, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotation in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Two by two, Holograph sketch in pencil with lyric; [1] p.; Note: additional holograph sketches include "Hold the moment" and unidentified material (Box-folder 5/1)
      - [Two by two], Holograph rhythmic sketch in pencil with crossed out lyric; [1] p.; On back: holograph sketch material designated as "Unused notes" (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Two by two: promenade, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Note: paper stained, damaged on p. [3] (Box-folder 5/2)
      - We're gonna be all right, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 5/3)
      - We're gonna be all right: refrain, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet, annotations in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 5/3)
      - We're gonna be all right, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Note: crossed out holograph sketch for "Story of my life" at top; and crossed out holograph sketch identified as "Thinking (New opening) bars" on back (Box-folder 5/3)
      - What do we do? We fly!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [6] p.; Note: performance annotations on p. [7] (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Planes 1; Planes 2, Holograph piano-vocal sketch and sketch with lyric, in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 5/4)
      - [Sketches for Do I Hear a Waltz?], Holograph sketches in pencil; [6] p.; Includes: p. [1]: "Take the moment" p. [2]: "Perhaps" p. [4]: "Goodbye tune: act II" p. [5]: "[What do we do? We fly!]: Planes" p. [6]: "[Two by two: promenade]: Eddie and Jennifer sect. of Promenade" (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Ever Green (1930; film [ Evergreen ], 1934) lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - Barker; [Quand notre vieux monde etait tout neuf] = When the old world was new, Holograph piano-vocal scores in pencil, no lyrics; 5 p.; 3 p. (Box-folder 5/6)
      - The beauty contest see: Opening act one
      - The colo[u]r of her eyes See also: [M.S. 2] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Note: same music as "The color of her eyes" which was cut from Spring Is Here (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Insert "Dancing on the ceiling" See also: Dancing on the ceiling in Simple Simon, Holograph melody in ink, with lyric; [8] m.; Note: cut from Simple Simon and used in Ever Green; Uniform title: Dancing on the ceiling (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Little clog: waltz, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [2] p.; Uniform title: Doing a little clog dance (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Lovely woman's ever young: The captain is a little baby, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Uniform title: La femme a toujours vingt ans! (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Harlemania, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 5/11)
      - If I give in to you, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [3] p. (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Talking song, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [2] p.; On back: holograph sketch for "Dance for Opening act one"; Uniform title: Impromptu song (Box-folder 5/13)